Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، وذبل إلى أشلاء♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ومع ذلك، ما زلتُ لا أجد لك أثراً♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪كحوت يغرق في شقوق أعماق البحر♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، فأفقد نفسي تماماً♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، وذبل إلى أشلاء♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك.
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
أصرخ وأنا أسقط في أحلك هاوية.
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪صدى الصوت ليس إلا موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪أبالغ في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 23=
=الحلقة 23=
(Puyuan Pastries)
(مخبز بويوان)
Boss.
رئيس.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
How many pieces of Pu Cake today?
كم قطعة من كعكة بو اليوم؟
Teach me.
علمني.
I want to make it myself today.
أريد أن أصنعها بنفسي اليوم.
Gently.
بلطف.
Done.
منتهي.
(Fu / Pu)
(فو / بو)
♪Maybe we didn't make the right choice back then♪
♪ربما لم نتخذ القرار الصحيح حينها♪
♪All that burning passion blindly followed you♪
♪كل ذلك الشغف المتأجج تبعك بشكل أعمى♪
♪Now that things have come to this, there's nothing left to say♪
♪الآن وقد وصلت الأمور إلى هذا الحد، لم يعد هناك ما يقال♪
♪Nothing we can do♪
♪لا شيء يمكننا فعله♪
♪All my joys and sorrows were decided by your words♪
♪كل أفراحي وأحزاني كانت تُحدد بكلماتك♪
♪Conflicting emotions tearing me apart♪
مشاعر متضاربة تمزقني إرباً
♪This numb heart♪
♪هذا القلب الخاوي♪
♪Only aches at times to remind me♪
♪ألمٌ بين الحين والآخر ليذكرني♪
♪What's wrong? You're silent again♪
♪ما الخطب؟ أنت صامت مجدداً♪
♪What pitiful role are you playing this time?♪
♪ما هو الدور البائس الذي تلعبه هذه المرة؟♪
♪Forgive all the sadness♪
♪سامح كل الحزن♪
♪Perfectly repeating it once more♪
♪تكرارها بشكل مثالي مرة أخرى♪
♪I won't say more. I'm tired, I'm worn out♪
لن أقول المزيد. أنا متعب، أنا منهك.
♪Let's just end this♪
♪لننهي هذا الأمر♪
♪You cry and laugh♪
♪تبكي وتضحك♪
(Liang Yi, look at me.)
(ليانغ يي، انظر إليّ.)
(You do love me, right?)
(أنت تحبني، أليس كذلك؟)
(What love or not love?)
(ما هو الحب أو عدم الحب؟)
(For the sake of protecting myself.)
(من أجل حماية نفسي.)
♪You know it all♪
♪أنت تعرف كل شيء♪
♪Don't wait anymore, forget the past♪
♪لا تنتظر أكثر، انسَ الماضي♪
♪Remember to live well♪
♪تذكر أن تعيش حياة طيبة♪
♪Hold back your tears as you turn around♪
♪اكبح دموعك وأنت تستدير♪
♪You said you would still miss me♪
♪قلتَ إنك ستشتاق إليّ♪
♪Just not love me anymore♪
♪لا تحبني بعد الآن♪
(I'm sorry.)
(أنا آسف.)
(I can't drag you down anymore.)
(لم أعد أستطيع أن أثقل كاهلك.)
♪I won't say more. I'm tired, I'm worn out♪
لن أقول المزيد. أنا متعب، أنا منهك.
♪Let's end this♪
♪لننهي هذا♪
♪You cry and laugh♪
♪تبكي وتضحك♪
♪But in the end, you still walked away♪
♪لكن في النهاية، ما زلتَ ترحل♪
♪I'll feel reluctant too♪
سأشعر بالتردد أيضاً
♪There'll be sadness, loneliness♪
♪سيكون هناك حزن ووحدة♪
♪You know it all♪
♪أنت تعرف كل شيء♪
♪Don't wait anymore, forget the past♪
♪لا تنتظر أكثر، انسَ الماضي♪
♪Remember to live well♪
♪تذكر أن تعيش حياة طيبة♪
♪Hold back your tears as you turn around♪
♪اكبح دموعك وأنت تستدير♪
♪You said you would still miss me♪
♪قلتَ إنك ستشتاق إليّ♪
(I will always protect you.)
(سأحميك دائماً.)
(Let's get married.)
(هيا نتزوج.)
I'll marry you.
سأتزوجك.
(I want everyone in Rong City to know)
(أريد أن يعلم الجميع في مدينة رونغ)
(that you are my woman.)
(أنكِ امرأتي).
I'll use my blood
سأستخدم دمي
to wash away all the dirt from your past.
لغسل كل الأوساخ من ماضيك.
(No lies.)
(لا أكاذيب.)
(No betrayal.)
(لا خيانة.)
(I will become the one you trust most.)
(سأصبح الشخص الذي تثق به أكثر من غيره.)
(Little Fox. Next time, just tell me directly what you want.)
(أيها الثعلب الصغير، في المرة القادمة، أخبرني مباشرة بما تريد.)
Not this one, not this.
ليس هذا، ليس هذا.
The others,
والآخرون،
get one of each
احصل على واحدة من كل نوع
in her size.
بحجمها.
(Is there really no such thing as karma in this world?)
(هل حقاً لا يوجد شيء اسمه الكارما في هذا العالم؟)
(If there isn't,)
(إن لم يكن هناك،)
(I'll fight for justice on your behalf.)
(سأناضل من أجل تحقيق العدالة نيابة عنك.)
(Don't worry.)
(لا تقلق.)
(We will definitely escape.)
(سنهرب بالتأكيد.)
(Even if it costs my life,)
(حتى لو كلفني ذلك حياتي،)
(I will get her out safely.)
(سأخرجها سالمة.)
(No matter what you've become,)
(بغض النظر عما أصبحت عليه،)
(the one I have always loved is still you.)
(الشخص الذي أحببته دائماً هو أنت).
(Liang Yi.)
(ليانغ يي.)
Lin Yun,
لين يون،
What we have was a transaction from the start.
ما لدينا كان صفقة منذ البداية.
Once I avenge myself,
بمجرد أن أنتقم لنفسي،
and you get what you want,
وستحصل على ما تريد،
there will be nothing between us anymore.
لن يكون هناك شيء بيننا بعد الآن.
(Without you,)
(بدونك،)
(I can live just fine.)
(يمكنني أن أعيش حياة جيدة تماماً.)
(We agreed not to interfere.)
(اتفقنا على عدم التدخل.)
(Mr. Lin, you should follow your own boundaries.)
(سيد لين، عليك أن تلتزم بحدودك الخاصة.)
Have you ever,
هل سبق لك أن
even for a moment, truly cared for me?
هل اهتم بي حقاً ولو للحظة؟
I'm sorry, Lin Yun.
أنا آسف يا لين يون.
My choice is
خياري هو
to let you go.
لأتركك تذهب.
(Clearly, I was the one who pushed you away.)
(من الواضح أنني كنت أنا من دفعك بعيداً.)
(I chose hatred.)
(اخترت الكراهية.)
(But,)
(لكن،)
(why does my heart hurt so much?)
(لماذا يؤلمني قلبي كثيراً؟)
(It feels like it's being torn apart alive.)
(يبدو الأمر كما لو أنه يتمزق وهو حي.)
(Was I wrong?)
(هل كنت مخطئاً؟)
(What am I supposed to do?)
(ماذا يفترض بي أن أفعل؟)
I said
قلت
if you don't come, I won't leave.
إذا لم تأتِ، فلن أغادر.
♪Between the lines of words♪
♪بين سطور الكلمات♪
♪Telling fragments of love and sorrow♪
♪أروي شذرات من الحب والحزن♪
♪Sun, moon, and stars♪
♪الشمس والقمر والنجوم♪
♪Speak not, for it is longing♪
لا تتكلم، فهذا شوق
♪Loneliness sealed in dust♪
♪وحدةٌ محصورةٌ في الغبار♪
♪The longer it stays, the deeper it grows♪
كلما طالت مدة بقائه، كلما ازداد عمقه
♪Seeing through all worldly things♪
♪رؤية ما وراء كل الأشياء الدنيوية♪
♪All sorrow fades into nothingness♪
♪كل الأحزان تتلاشى في العدم♪
♪A lover's deep affection♪
♪مودة عميقة من الحبيب♪
♪Dwelling deep in my heart♪
♪يسكن في أعماق قلبي♪
♪Nowhere to hide♪
♪لا مكان للاختباء♪
♪Loveless, yet fearing too much feeling♪
♪بلا حب، ومع ذلك يخشى الشعور المفرط♪
♪Loved you until it became a curse on my heart♪
أحببتك حتى أصبح حبي لعنة على قلبي
♪Couldn't win your heart, so I foolishly tore myself down♪
لم أستطع الفوز بقلبك، لذلك حطمت نفسي بحماقة.
♪My beloved is without fault♪
♪حبيبي بلا عيب♪
♪To understand is already so rare♪
♪إن الفهم أصبح نادراً جداً♪
♪Holding tight to what's not yours♪
♪التمسك بشدة بما ليس لك♪
♪Letting go of what wouldn't leave♪
التخلي عما لم يكن ليرحل
♪No use persuading, one thought and the obsession deepens♪
♪لا جدوى من الإقناع، فكرة واحدة ويتعمق الهوس♪
♪Beloved, at this moment the southeast stretches endlessly♪
♪يا حبيبي، في هذه اللحظة يمتد الجنوب الشرقي بلا نهاية♪
How were you so certain back then
كيف كنت متأكدًا إلى هذا الحد في ذلك الوقت؟
that I would definitely acknowledge Song Ming to save my life?
هل سأعترف بالتأكيد لسونغ مينغ لإنقاذ حياتي؟
Weren't you afraid I'd fall into utter despair and only seek death?
ألم تكن تخشى أن أقع في يأسٍ تام ولا أسعى إلا للموت؟
You wouldn't.
لن تفعل ذلك.
You would only hate me.
لن تكرهني إلا.
The more you hate me,
كلما ازداد كرهك لي،
the more you'd want to live, just to take revenge on me.
كلما زادت رغبتك في الحياة، فقط للانتقام مني.
Why are you so foolish?
لماذا أنت أحمق إلى هذا الحد؟
Foolish enough to think I'd really bear to take revenge on you?
هل أنت أحمق بما يكفي لتظن أنني سأتحمل حقاً الانتقام منك؟
I think you bore it just fine.
أعتقد أنك تجيد ذلك تماماً.
That day at the Song Residence,
في ذلك اليوم في منزل عائلة سونغ،
you asked me if I was also acting.
سألتني إن كنت أمثل أيضاً.
Song Ming was right outside the door. Did you know?
كان سونغ مينغ يقف خارج الباب مباشرةً. هل تعلم؟
You almost got me killed.
كادت أن تتسبب في موتي.
But at the moment you asked me,
لكن في اللحظة التي سألتني فيها،
my heart warmed.
شعرتُ بدفء في قلبي.
Because it made me feel that you still trusted me.
لأن ذلك جعلني أشعر بأنك ما زلت تثق بي.
So everything you did
إذن كل ما فعلته
was to deceive Song Ming?
كان الهدف هو خداع سونغ مينغ؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Song Ming has been secretly colluding with Yunzhou for a long time.
كان سونغ مينغ يتآمر سراً مع يونتشو لفترة طويلة.
The opium was merely
لم يكن الأفيون سوى
one of the channels he used to funnel benefits to Yunzhou.
إحدى القنوات التي استخدمها لتوجيه المنافع إلى يونتشو.
What he wants is Yunzhou's military force,
ما يريده هو القوة العسكرية ليونتشو،
to help him seize Jiangzhou.
لمساعدته في الاستيلاء على جيانغتشو.
So you helped him amass money quickly
إذن فقد ساعدته في جمع المال بسرعة
just to push him into rebellion?
فقط لدفعه إلى التمرد؟
Yes.
نعم.
But what if he really succeeded in taking Jiangzhou?
لكن ماذا لو نجح بالفعل في الاستيلاء على جيانغتشو؟
He won't succeed.
لن ينجح.
Did you really think
هل كنت تعتقد حقاً
I'd hand that money to Yunzhou?
هل سأعطي ذلك المال ليونتشو؟
What I wanted
ما أردته
was merely proof of his exposed ambition.
كان ذلك مجرد دليل على طموحه المكشوف.
Lin Yun,
لين يون،
promise me,
وعدني،
let me deliver the final blow.
دعني أوجه الضربة القاضية.
The one who killed my father
الشخص الذي قتل والدي
was Song Ming.
كان سونغ مينغ.
Yi.
يفعل.
Having porridge again?
هل ستتناول العصيدة مرة أخرى؟
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Last time after we had porridge, we separated.
في المرة الأخيرة، بعد أن تناولنا العصيدة، انفصلنا.
This time the flavor is different.
هذه المرة النكهة مختلفة.
You're like a dog.
أنت مثل الكلب.
If you run off again,
إذا هربت مرة أخرى،
I'll...
سوف...
Are you bringing the chain to lock me to the bed?
هل ستحضر السلسلة لتقييدي بالسرير؟
Would you bear to?
هل تتحمل ذلك؟
Then swear it
ثم أقسم بذلك
that you'll never leave me again.
أنك لن تتركني مرة أخرى.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I swear.
أقسم.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless I die.
إلا إذا مت.
Liang Yi.
ليانغ يي.
I was just joking.
كنت أمزح فقط.
I promise you,
أعدك،
I'll live until all our teeth fall out,
سأعيش حتى تسقط جميع أسناننا،
and I'll keep pestering you, alright?
وسأظل ألح عليك، حسناً؟
Why must you go to Yunzhou?
لماذا يجب عليك الذهاب إلى يونتشو؟
If I don't go,
إذا لم أذهب،
Song Ming will grow suspicious.
سيبدأ سونغ مينغ بالشك.
What if Marshal Jin finds out?
ماذا لو اكتشف المارشال جين الأمر؟
This is the arrangement between me and Marshal Jin.
هذا هو الاتفاق بيني وبين مارشال جين.
You still need to stay cautious.
لا يزال عليك توخي الحذر.
When I left the Song Residence,
عندما غادرت مقر إقامة سونغ،
did Song Ming get suspicious?
هل ساور سونغ مينغ الشك؟
No.
لا.
I told him I had you locked up by my side
قلت له إنني حبستك بجانبي
and was torturing you hard.
وكان يعذبك بشدة.
When are you leaving?
متى ستغادر؟
The afternoon boat.
قارب ما بعد الظهر.
Come with me to a place.
تعال معي إلى مكان ما.
This fabric suits me.
هذا القماش يناسبني.
I'll make you a summer shirt.
سأصنع لك قميصًا صيفيًا.
Madam, you truly have good taste.
سيدتي، ذوقكِ رفيع حقاً.
The collar needs silver cloud embroidery.
يحتاج طوق الياقة إلى تطريز سحابة فضية.
Noted.
ذُكر.
The waist shouldn't be made too wide.
لا ينبغي أن يكون الخصر عريضاً جداً.
You can do this too?
هل يمكنك فعل هذا أيضاً؟
I used to measure all my father's clothes.
كنت أقيس جميع ملابس والدي.
Madam, please look here.
سيدتي، انظري هنا من فضلك.
Spring silk.
حرير الربيع.
Summer gauze.
شاش صيفي.
Autumn velvet.
مخمل الخريف.
Winter fur.
فراء الشتاء.
All are here.
الجميع هنا.
Yunzhou is spring all year round.
تتمتع مدينة يونتشو بجو ربيعي طوال العام.
You've prepared clothes for all four seasons.
لقد جهزت ملابس لجميع الفصول الأربعة.
What is all this for?
ما الهدف من كل هذا؟
You wear those black suits all the time.
أنت ترتدي تلك البدلات السوداء طوال الوقت.
I'm sick of seeing them.
لقد سئمت من رؤيتهم.
Naturally, these are for you to wear in the future.
بالطبع، هذه الأشياء مخصصة لك لارتدائها في المستقبل.
I should go.
ينبغي عليّ الذهاب.
Be good and wait for me to come back.
كن مطيعاً وانتظر عودتي.
Safe travels.
رحلة سعيدة.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Governor Song ordered that you don't need to go to Yunzhou.
أصدر الحاكم سونغ قراراً بعدم ضرورة ذهابكم إلى يونتشو.
Please come with us.
تفضل بالانضمام إلينا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
No need to go to Yunzhou.
لا داعي للذهاب إلى يونتشو.
Good son.
ابن بار.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
Yunzhou's troops have already entered Rong City.
دخلت قوات يونتشو مدينة رونغ بالفعل.
Too bad.
سيئة للغاية.
Your performance failed.
لقد فشلت في أدائك.
You said you were going to Yunzhou in my place.
قلتَ إنك ستذهب إلى يونتشو بدلاً مني.
Were you planning to take my life?
هل كنت تخطط لقتلي؟
Tell me, was ancestral grave of the Song family chosen wrong?
أخبرني، هل تم اختيار قبر أجداد عائلة سونغ بشكل خاطئ؟
One son reckless and stupid at birth,
ولد واحد طائش وغبي عند ولادته،
and then you,
ثم أنت،
a dagger hidden at the end.
خنجر مخبأ في النهاية.
Scheming every day to kill your old man.
يخططون كل يوم لقتل والدك.
You hid something inside the banner. Don't think I don't know.
لقد أخفيت شيئاً داخل اللافتة. لا تظن أنني لا أعرف.
(Proof)
(دليل)
With this proof, come to Chengyun Society in a month,
بهذا الدليل، تعال إلى جمعية تشنغيون خلال شهر.
and reclaim all the property on the donation agreement.
واستعادة جميع الممتلكات المنصوص عليها في اتفاقية التبرع.
The deeds.
الأفعال.
One month.
شهر واحد.
You calculated it perfectly.
لقد حسبتها بدقة متناهية.
You're waiting for me to be dead,
أنت تنتظر موتي،
then return everything to you.
ثم أعيد كل شيء إليك.
Will Yunzhou give it back to you?
هل ستعيد يونتشو إليك ما تحتاجه؟
When their troops surround Jiangzhou,
عندما تحاصر قواتهم مدينة جيانغتشو،
do you think they'll agree?
هل تعتقد أنهم سيوافقون؟
Who will surround it?
من سيحيط بها؟
Your Chengyun Society?
مجتمع تشنغيون الخاص بك؟
Tell me, who?
أخبرني، من؟
A treacherous minister starts a rebellion,
وزير خائن يبدأ تمرداً،
who will suppress it?
من سيقمعها؟
So you've already colluded with Marshal Jin in secret.
إذن فقد تواطأت بالفعل مع المارشال جين سراً.
Planning to join forces to eliminate me.
يخططون لتوحيد الجهود للقضاء عليّ.
Cruel enough.
قاسٍ بما فيه الكفاية.
A small-time gangster like you,
مجرم صغير مثلك،
Marshal Jin is probably being played by you as well.
ربما أنت أيضاً تلعب دور المارشال جين.
You want to borrow someone else's knife
تريد استعارة سكين شخص آخر
to kill your own father, right?
أن تقتل والدك، أليس كذلك؟
It seems
يبدو
you are even more ruthless than Zhichu.
أنت أكثر قسوة من زيتشو.
Tell me, what have I been fighting for half my life?
أخبرني، ما الذي كنت أقاتل من أجله طوال نصف حياتي؟
What's the point?
ما الفائدة من ذلك؟
Meaningless.
لا معنى له.
Even if I become Marshal,
حتى لو أصبحتُ مارشالاً،
no one will take the position of Young Marshal.
لن يتولى أحد منصب المارشال الشاب.
Marshal?
مارشال؟
You think you deserve it?
أتظن أنك تستحق ذلك؟
Why did the Marshal's position go to Jin back then,
لماذا ذهب منصب المارشال إلى جين آنذاك؟
and not you?
وليس أنت؟
You really don't know?
ألا تعلم حقاً؟
You didn't even dare raise your own troops.
لم تجرؤ حتى على تجنيد قواتك الخاصة.
You paid Yunzhou to buy soldiers.
لقد دفعت ليونتشو لشراء الجنود.
Aren't you afraid they'll swallow you whole later?
ألا تخشى أن يبتلعوك بالكامل لاحقاً؟
You let your son kill and burn for you,
سمحت لابنك أن يقتل ويحرق من أجلك،
and when he died, you called him stupid.
وعندما مات، وصفته بالغبي.
Song Ming.
سونغ مينغ.
Your dream of being Marshal is utterly ridiculous.
حلمك بأن تصبح مارشال أمر سخيف للغاية.
Shut up!
اسكت!
(Presented to Mr. Wang Jiangzhou Honorary Citizen)
(مقدمة إلى السيد وانغ جيانغتشو، المواطن الفخري)
(Good Man of Rong City By Lin Yun of Chengyun Society)
(رجل رونغ الطيب، بقلم لين يون من جمعية تشنغيون)
Song Ming already sent the money to Yunzhou long ago.
أرسل سونغ مينغ المال إلى يونتشو منذ فترة طويلة.
They say Yunzhou's troops have entered Rong City.
يقولون إن قوات يونتشو دخلت مدينة رونغ.
Any news of Lin Yun and Song Ming?
هل من أخبار عن لين يون وسونغ مينغ؟
The boss's life or death is unknown.
مصير الرئيس مجهول، سواء أكان حياً أم ميتاً.
Break in!
يقتحم!
Rescue the boss!
أنقذ الزعيم!
Song Ming won't fight to the death.
لن يقاتل سونغ مينغ حتى الموت.
He's not that determined.
إنه ليس مصمماً إلى هذا الحد.
Everyone.
الجميع.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
Yes, Madam Lin.
نعم، سيدتي لين.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Who's there?
من هناك؟
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪♪
♪ارفعوا الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأوا عرضكم المتكلف♪♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪أغبى مقامر♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪سيتعامل مع الحب كفريسة، ولا يبالي بشيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء لا تزال حاضرة في ذهني.
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪يا لها من هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪يُكشف عن النصر بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪ونسقط كلانا في عزلة لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪أحببتُ بعمقٍ شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
أساليبك قاسية للغاية
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لا ينتظرك إلا العار♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪ونسقط كلانا في عزلة لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪أحببتُ بعمقٍ شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
أساليبك قاسية للغاية
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لا ينتظرك إلا العار♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪نداء الستار♪